<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>NWSLTR-2023FY-CHBC-BAS-Partner-Essentials.Email #1 (With mental health needs on</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>With mental health needs on the rise, it&apos;s time to step up services</subject>
    <textOnly>May 2023

Partner Essentials

Teladoc Health launches Provider-Based Care for Weight Management &amp; Prediabetes solutions
Teladoc Health recently announced the expansion of Provider-Based Care for our Weight Management and Prediabetes programs. With 42% of adults in the United States living with obesity, this expansion aims to drive better health outcomes while addressing the growing cost associated with obesity and weight management.

Read our press release here. &lt;[[https://business.teladochealth.com/newsroom/press/release/Teladoc-Health-Launches-Provider-Based-Care-for-Weight-Management--Prediabetes-Programs/?&amp;utm_source=marketo&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_content=Teladoc-Health-Launches-Provider-Based-Care-for-Weight-Management--Prediabetes-Programs&amp;utm_term=&amp;utm_campaign=may-partner-essentials-consultant&amp;utm_campaign_id=]]&gt;

Provider-Based Care is the natural evolution of our chronic condition management solutions, integrating Teladoc Health’s extensive provider network to deliver the right care at the right time for high-risk members. It was launched earlier this year for the Diabetes Management and Hypertension solutions and will be expanded into Weight Management and Prediabetes later this year. This new feature is an add on, opt in, at no additional cost for
Teladoc Health clients.

Provider-Based Care is designed to help members get back into clinical control by losing weight as well as preventing and managing diabetes. By safely optimizing medications, such as glucagon-like peptide (GLP-1) agonists and sodium-glucose cotransporter-2 (SGLT2) inhibitors, the program works in conjunction with the range of Teladoc Health solutions and tools that address the foundational pillars impacting cardiometabolic health.

Resources
Interview with an expert: Meet Teladoc Health&apos;s
MaryBlake Williams &lt;[[https://view.highspot.com/viewer/645e9e68c3cfeef16fa3490c]]&gt;
I’m excited to be at Teladoc Health, to meet you and to help your clients find the right solutions for their virtual care needs—especially when it comes to providing more people access to the quality mental healthcare they need.

Accessible mental healthcare can be altogether life-changing &lt;[[https://business.teladochealth.com/resources/video/accessible-mental-health-care-can-be-altogether-life-changing/?&amp;utm_source=marketo&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_content=accessible-mental-health-care-can-be-altogether-life-changing&amp;utm_term=&amp;utm_campaign=may-partner-essentials-consultant&amp;utm_campaign_id=]]&gt;
Hear firsthand how our members experience mental health services from Teladoc Health.

ON DEMAND WEBINAR: Mental Health awareness &lt;[[https://view.highspot.com/viewer/64653d65e8c5a4f7e3c264cc]]&gt;
In this short presentation, learn about some important mental health trends affecting those seeking treatment, specifically around accessibility, affordability, approachability and equity.

An integrated whole-person benefits strategy to help employees live their best lives &lt;[[https://business.teladochealth.com/resources/case-study/an-integrated-whole-person-benefits-strategy/?&amp;utm_source=marketo&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_content=an-integrated-whole-person-benefits-strategy&amp;utm_term=&amp;utm_campaign=may-partner-essentials-consultant&amp;utm_campaign_id=]]&gt;
This employer turned to Teladoc Health to simplify the benefits process and help employees achieve exponentially better physical and mental health clinical outcomes.

In the news
New study from Teladoc Health further validates the effectiveness of a single, integrated care experience &lt;[[https://business.teladochealth.com/newsroom/press/release/New-Study-from-Teladoc-Health-Further-Validates-the-Effectiveness-of-a-Single-Integrated-Care-Experience/?&amp;utm_source=marketo&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_content=New-Study-from-Teladoc-Health-Further-Validates-the-Effectiveness-of-a-Single-Integrated-Care-Experience&amp;utm_term=&amp;utm_campaign=may-partner-essentials-consultant&amp;utm_campaign_id=]]&gt;

Virtual primary care: the new frontier of healthcare delivery &lt;[[https://medcitynews.com/2023/05/virtual-primary-care/]]&gt;

Foundry’s CIO recently named Teladoc Health as a 2023 CIO 100 Award Winner &lt;[[https://foundryco.com/news/cio-celebrates-innovations-in-business-technology-with-2023-cio-100-hall-of-fame-awards/]]&gt;

Fast fact
Chronic illnesses affect half of the population, and the care needed to treat these conditions accounts for more than 85% of healthcare costs. &lt;[[https://www.benefitspro.com/2023/02/14/how-employers-are-side-stepping-rising-health-care-costs-with-virtual-care/]]&gt;

About Teladoc Health: Teladoc Health is transforming the healthcare experience and empowering people everywhere to live healthier lives. Recognized as the world leader in whole-person virtual care, Teladoc Health leverages more than a decade of expertise and data-driven insights to meet the growing virtual care needs of consumers and healthcare professionals.

twitter &lt;[[https://twitter.com/teladochealth]]&gt; Linkedin &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/teladoc-health/]]&gt;

Unsubscribe &lt;[[https://go1.teladochealth.com/subscriptions.html]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[https://teladochealth.com/privacy-policy/]]&gt; | Legal Notice &lt;[[https://teladochealth.com/notice-of-non-discrimination/]]&gt;

© Teladoc Health, Inc. All rights reserved. 2 Manhattanville Road, Purchase, NY 10577</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
